vois.com 2010-11-01

# Project Outsourcing Websites, Freelancers, Freelance Programming, Hire Freelance Programmer, Outsourcing Web Designing

|  | 

### VOIS Privacy Policy

| 

(Version 2007.05) 

VOIS, INC. ("VOIS") operates a social commerce (or "sCommerce") network Website located at http://www.vois.com/ and any other VOIS-branded services provided to you by VOIS (the VOIS Website and other VOIS-branded services are together referred to as the "Website"). The Website is an online service that connects our members together both socially and economically. VOIS members can profile their lives online, view each other's profiles, and connect with others around shared social and economic interests. VOIS members can make unlimited friends and connections and then use those connections to connect personally and do business with others on a whole new level. VOIS members can change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them.

This Privacy Policy provides VOIS' policies and procedures with respect to the collection and use of your personally identifiable information as a user of the Website, as well as what choices you have about its use. Use of the Website is governed by the TERMS OF USE (located at http://www.vois.com/default/termsOfUse/), which incorporates this Privacy Policy by reference. In this regard, acceptance of the TERMS OF USE constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy, all as expressly provided in the TERMS OF USE.

By accepting the TERMS OF USE and therefore this Privacy Policy, you hereby confirm that you know that the Website is a website operated by VOIS in the U.S., and you consent to the transfer of your personal data to the U.S., where your personal data will be subject to U.S. law and, if you live outside of the U.S., where the level of data protection may be different compared to your country.

VOIS places the highest priority on online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy@vois.com](mailto:privacy@vois.com "privacy@vois.com").

**Notice to California Residents:** Under California Law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship, (1) a list of the categories of information, such as name, address, e-mail address, and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes, and (2) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information, please write to us with a reference to California Disclosure Information at: Legal Department, VOIS, Inc., 255 N.E. 6th Avenue, Delray Beach, FL 33483.

**Minors:** Minors - as defined by the laws of your jurisdiction -- are prohibited from using this site. We do not knowing collect information from any minor.   
  
---  
**TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**  

**Registration Information**

As described in the TERMS OF USE, you may use the Website as a "Visitor" (which means you are just browsing the Website) or a "Registered Member" (which means you have registered as a member of the Website). In order to register as a member of the Website, you must complete the online registration form and create a password and unique user name. During registration you are also required to give personally identifiable information including your first name, last name, email address, state, postal code and date of birth. We use this information to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the Website. Some of your registration information also becomes part of your Personal Profile.

**Personal Profile Information**

If you are a Registered Member, you have the option to provide profile information about yourself, such as your personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation, which refer to as your "Personal Profile". We encourage you to submit relevant information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in your Personal Profile. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

**Pictures**

If you are a Registered Member, you have the option to add one or more pictures to your Personal Profile. Each picture can be designated as public or private (in which case, only your "friends" can see the picture). You also can designate one picture as your "Main Profile Picture". Your Main Profile Picture (if you provide one) is always viewable by Visitors and Registered Members.

**Promotions, Contests or Surveys**

From time-to-time you may be offered the opportunity to participate in a promotion, contest or survey on the Website (we will refer to all of these activities as "Promotions"). If you participate in a Promotion, we (or a third party identified by VOIS), may request additional information from you - including personally identifiable information.

**Invitations and Other Communications to Non-Members**

We may offer you a referral service to tell a friend (on the Website, "Friends" are also referred to as "Connections") about our site. If you choose to use our referral service, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend an initial email inviting him or her to visit the Website. VOIS will store your friend's name and email address so that your friend may be added to your "friend's list", and also to send reminders of the invitations. VOIS will not sell the email addresses you provide for referrals or use that information to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders (up to three (3) per email address). Recipients of invitations from VOIS will be able to contact us at [privacy@vois.com](mailto:privacy@vois.com "privacy@vois.com") to request that we remove this information from our database.

**Information from Other Sources**

From time to time, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. For example, we may receive confirmations or other feedback from third parties engaged in Promotions. Additionally, we may purchase demographic information about you to allow us to provide you personalized offerings. We also may obtain search term and search result information from some searches conducted through the Web search features; search results and links, including paid listings (such as sponsored links from Google).

**Website Traffic Information**

We may also collect and analyze the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, login, email address, password, computer and connection information, browser type and version, operating system. We also we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. We collect this information from Visitors and Registered Members, typically through automated methods.

**Cookies and Pixel Tags**

A cookie is a small piece of information that a Website can send to your browser and may then be stored on your computer's hard drive. It acts as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer, but not you personally. A pixel tag, also known as a clear GIF or web beacon, is an invisible tag placed on certain pages of the Website but not on your computer. When you access these pages, pixel tags generate a generic notice of that visit. They usually work in conjunction with cookies, registering when a particular computer visits a particular page. If you turn off cookies the pixel tag will simply detect an anonymous Website visit and certain features of the Website may not be available.

**Third Party Advertisers**

The advertisements appearing on this Website may be delivered to users by our advertisers. We share Website usage information about users for the purpose of targeting our advertisements on the Website.

Our advertisers may use cookies and/or clear GIFs. These cookies and clear GIFs allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on.

This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. The information that our advertisers collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by VOIS and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

We may transfer personal information to certain of our advertisers that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.  
  
**USE, SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION.**  

**Personal Information Always Shown**

Registered Member information is displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the VOIS sCommerce community. The following personal information is always viewable by Visitors and Registered Members: your display name and Main Profile Picture. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service (discussed in more detail below), the Website allows users to search for other members using criteria, such as first and last name, age, email address, and schools and/or companies where users may have attended or worked, but only if and to the extent that you provide such information. The following sections describe additional information that may be viewable by others.

**Viewing Personal Profile and Other Information**

Visitors and Registered Members each by default may view all of your Personal Profile information (other than your date of birth), Registration Information, your presence online, who are your "friends", and your pictures (including your Main Profile Picture). You may, however, restrict access to this information through VOIS's Privacy Settings in the following ways:

  * You may hide your presence online (that is, designate that others will not be told by VOIS that you are currently online and actively viewing the Website).
  * You may specify who can view your birthday: (a) only you; (b) only your friends; or (c) Everyone. By default, Visitors and Registered Members (including your friends) can see your birthday.
  * You can specify who can see your Personal Profile: (a) everyone (which is the default setting) or (b) only your friends. If you specify that only your friends can view your Personal Profile, then the only information about you that will be displayed is your Main Profile Picture (if you provide one) and your display name.
  * You also may designate one or more Pictures as "Private".

**Searching Personal Profiles**

The Website includes features that allow Visitors and Registered Members to search for your profile based on your first name, last name, display name, email address, state, city, zip code, country, date of birth, gender, age, your "Friends" and all your Personal Profile Information. If your Profile matches the search criteria it will be listed in the search results. As noted above, the information presented with your profile depends upon your privacy settings, and whether the person conducting the search is a Visitor, Registered Member or your "friend". (Note, certain information about you, while not displayed, may be discoverable by specific or repeated searches).

**Service Providers**

We use third parties to provide certain administrative and service-related services on our site. These third parties may have access to all of your personal information. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

**Promotional Offers**

Occasionally we send offers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Unless we provide you notice of other terms, this Privacy Policy will control the disclosure and use of the information collected during the Promotion.

**Providing Personalized Services to You**

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, Internet Traffic Information and/or third party sources to create a "profile" of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. We use cookies and pixel tags to identify you as a return visitor and optimize and track your use of the Site. Doing so helps us provide enhanced features such as accelerated purchasing, customized and personalized shopping suggestions, personalized greetings, and storage of items in your shopping bag between visits.

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. We also use this information, which does not alone identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, you can do so in the "Your Account Settings" area of your Personal Profile.

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies, and their use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the VOIS Privacy Policy.

**Business Transfers**

To improve the offerings and selection at the Website, we may occasionally acquire subsidiaries or particular business units may be bought by or merged with another entity, entities, or individuals. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy notice(s) (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the event that VOIS or substantially all of VOIS's or the Website's assets are acquired, all customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. VOIS reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of VOIS or substantially all of its or the Website's assets to that successor in interest.

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our business partners (including our advertisers). When sharing this information, we do not identify individual users

**Law Enforcement; Protection of VOIS Inc. and Others**

It is sometimes necessary to release account and other information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of VOIS, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Under no circumstances, however, does this include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from clients for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this privacy policy. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by VOIS, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the VOIS TERMS OF USE or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service.

**With Your Consent**

Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to elect whether or not to share the information.  
  
**COMMUNICATIONS FROM THE WEBSITE**  

**Communications Choice/Opt-out**

Other than Service-Related Announcements and Customer Service communications (each described below), you may elect not to receive updates or notifications from VOIS by unchecking "Send Me All Notifications" on your account's Account Settings page. You also may elect to receive only specific types of notifications, by checking one or more of the options available in Account Settings.

**Special Offers and Updates**

We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the "Your Account Settings" area of your Personal Profile.

**Newsletters**

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the "Your Account Settings" area of your Personal Profile.

**Service-related Announcements**

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

**Customer Service**

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not administrative in nature.  
  
**OTHER TERMS**  

**Links to Other Sites**

This Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by VOIS. Please be aware that VOIS is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Website and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Website.

**Co-Branded sites**

This Website may contain links to other sites that are co-branded together with a third party. In such cases, VOIS may or may not be responsible for the privacy practices of such co-branded sites. If VOIS is responsible for the privacy practices, then this Privacy Policy will apply. If VOIS is not responsible for the privacy practices and if the third party is not VOIS' agent or service provider covered under this Privacy Policy, then VOIS is not responsible for the privacy practices of such site. Again, we encourage you to be aware when you leave the Website and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information.

**Chat Rooms, Journals and Blogs, Message Boards, Classifieds and Public Forums**

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to your chat rooms, journals, blogs, message boards, classifieds or any other public forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. You have the option to securely access the Website at [http://www.vois.com](http://www.vois.com/ "https://www.vois.com").

If you have any questions about security on the Website, you can send email us at [privacy@vois.com](mailto:privacy@vois.com "privacy@vois.com").  
  
**USER CHOICES WITH REGARD TO ACCESS OF INFORMATION**  

You may correct, update or delete your Profile information, and update your registration information (other than with respect to your username) by logging into your account and accessing the "My Dashboard" option (available when logged in and viewing your Home Page).

**General**

You always have the right to refrain from providing any information (other than information required for registration). This may have an impact on use of the Website and on the ease of making, or ability to make, purchases or taking advantage of certain unique features of the Website. By providing information about third parties, you represent that you have all necessary authority and/or obtained all necessary consents from such person to authorize us to collect, use and disclose the information of such third parties. All such information shall be governed by the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Customer Communication**

If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us (other than required service-related announcements described above), then please adjust your account setting regarding email contact preferences (please see the "Your Account Settings" area of your Personal Profile). You cannot waive the applicability of the Terms of Use and other legal notices, such as this Privacy Notice, and if you elect not to receive those notices, they will still govern your use of the Website, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.

**Cookie Choices**

All Web browsers have the ability to accept cookies, reject cookies, or to prompt the user before accepting them. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, affecting the acceptance of cookies means that you may not be able to use such important features as accelerated ordering unless you leave them turned on.

**Anonymous Browsing**

A large number of products may be accessed without the use of cookies, or anonymously. In addition, the Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own Website, "[Site Seeing on the Internet](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.html "Site Seeing on the Internet")"

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post the modified Privacy Policy on this Website to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. A user is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the Website after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use a Registered Member's personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify by posting a notice on the Website for 30 days.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 951 Yamato Road, Suite 201, Boca Raton, Fl 33431 ; Facsimile: (561) 274-4895; and [privacy@vois.com](mailto:privacy@vois.com "privacy@vois.com").
